<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>terraform on Eric Fuerstenberg</title>
    <link>https://hierux.cloud/tags/terraform/</link>
    <description>Recent content in terraform on Eric Fuerstenberg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 17:33:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hierux.cloud/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating with Terraform and CodeShip</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/terraform-cicd-codeship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 17:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/terraform-cicd-codeship/</guid>
      <description>Tear it down and automate! Today I completely tore down my existing infrastructure for this static website and rebuilt the entire thing in Terraform! They say you never truly understand something until you can write automation, tear it down, and rebuild it in just a few minutes. See updates to the git repo here.
One step closer in the pursuit of everything-as-code!
This site still relies on the same underlying infrastructure: AWS S3 for static hosting, Route53 for DNS, and CloudFront for CDN and SSL, but I also integrated a CI/CD pipeline using CodeShip to automate the build and deployment of this website to my production S3 bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today I learned..</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/daily1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 08:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/daily1/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m up to today.  Studying python Alerts as code! Continuing my work on templatizing alerts and dashboards in Terraform, using the Wavefront TF provider integration. Creating a framework to programmatically manage all of my team&amp;rsquo;s active alerts and dashboards in Wavefront using Terraform. Making small tweaks to this Hugo site.  to-do list includes:  add an &amp;ldquo;about me&amp;rdquo; &amp;amp; skills section configure the infrastructure in terraform (s3 buckets, route53 dns assignments, cloudfront distribution) set up ci/cd pipeline using codeship for automatic deployments      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform, AWS, and other personal progress</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/historical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 08:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/historical/</guid>
      <description>Notes step by step: 04/15/20
1. working with terraform and ec2
- creating instances using amis
- running bootstrap script to configure instance as webserver
- configure security groups (ingress/egress on ports 80 &amp;amp; 443)
- assign security groups to ec2 instances
- capture public/private ips of instances as output
 to do:
1. configure this static side in hugo
2. set up s3 bucket for static hosting in aws and use terraform to manage this process</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>