<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cloud on Eric Fuerstenberg</title>
    <link>https://hierux.cloud/tags/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cloud on Eric Fuerstenberg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 17:33:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hierux.cloud/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating with Terraform and CodeShip</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/terraform-cicd-codeship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 17:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/terraform-cicd-codeship/</guid>
      <description>Tear it down and automate! Today I completely tore down my existing infrastructure for this static website and rebuilt the entire thing in Terraform! They say you never truly understand something until you can write automation, tear it down, and rebuild it in just a few minutes. See updates to the git repo here.
One step closer in the pursuit of everything-as-code!
This site still relies on the same underlying infrastructure: AWS S3 for static hosting, Route53 for DNS, and CloudFront for CDN and SSL, but I also integrated a CI/CD pipeline using CodeShip to automate the build and deployment of this website to my production S3 bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting a high performance static site with S3, Route53, &amp; SSL via CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/static-s3-ssl-cloudfront/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 14:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/static-s3-ssl-cloudfront/</guid>
      <description>Update: Hugo I recently reconfigured my static website (still hosted at cloud.hierux.com) into a more feature rich site using Hugo - you&amp;rsquo;re looking at it right now! This allows me to make use of style templates and other feature enhancements while keeping things simple with markdown.
You can find the Hugo-ified version of my website in my Github repo.
I&amp;rsquo;ve hosted static sites using a number of different strategies in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform, AWS, and other personal progress</title>
      <link>https://hierux.cloud/posts/historical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 08:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hierux.cloud/posts/historical/</guid>
      <description>Notes step by step: 04/15/20
1. working with terraform and ec2
- creating instances using amis
- running bootstrap script to configure instance as webserver
- configure security groups (ingress/egress on ports 80 &amp;amp; 443)
- assign security groups to ec2 instances
- capture public/private ips of instances as output
 to do:
1. configure this static side in hugo
2. set up s3 bucket for static hosting in aws and use terraform to manage this process</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>